[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "What's the very latest you're hearing about a U.S. Military strike?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "very", "latest", "you", "'re", "hearing", "about", "a", "U.S.", "Military", "strike", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Well, look, well, from the U.S. point of view, their contention that the White House is, they have the information in hand that could lead the President to make that decision.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "well", ",", "from", "the", "U.S.", "point", "of", "view", ",", "their", "contention", "that", "the", "White", "House", "is", ",", "they", "have", "the", "information", "in", "hand", "that", "could", "lead", "the", "President", "to", "make", "that", "decision", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Do we have any indication?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "have", "any", "indication", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well, certainly not I wouldn't think days.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", "not", "I", "would", "n't", "think", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Do you think this would be a mistake for the U.S. to act militarily, why?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "this", "would", "be", "a", "mistake", "for", "the", "U.S.", "to", "act", "militarily", ",", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "But let me get back to the suggestion that -- I think you were suggesting that maybe the opposition, the rebels, have been using chemical weapons, is there any evidence you've seen that they have?", "question_tokens": ["But", "let", "me", "get", "back", "to", "the", "suggestion", "that", "--", "I", "think", "you", "were", "suggesting", "that", "maybe", "the", "opposition", ",", "the", "rebels", ",", "have", "been", "using", "chemical", "weapons", ",", "is", "there", "any", "evidence", "you", "'ve", "seen", "that", "they", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "I hear allegations similar to that and I say I don't exclude that have taken place.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hear", "allegations", "similar", "to", "that", "and", "I", "say", "I", "do", "n't", "exclude", "that", "have", "taken", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "So when they present this evidence publicly today to the American people, to the international community, as far as you're concerned that's not good enough?", "question_tokens": ["So", "when", "they", "present", "this", "evidence", "publicly", "today", "to", "the", "American", "people", ",", "to", "the", "international", "community", ",", "as", "far", "as", "you", "'re", "concerned", "that", "'s", "not", "good", "enough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "I'm not sure that the American people want to be the world police.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "that", "the", "American", "people", "want", "to", "be", "the", "world", "police", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Do you think it's possible he's right again this time?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "possible", "he", "'s", "right", "again", "this", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "For you, did you hear the actual voice of Syrian commanders speaking about ordering chemical weapons to be used?", "question_tokens": ["For", "you", ",", "did", "you", "hear", "the", "actual", "voice", "of", "Syrian", "commanders", "speaking", "about", "ordering", "chemical", "weapons", "to", "be", "used", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "No, we did not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "did", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Was that good enough for you then?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "good", "enough", "for", "you", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well, look, I think to compare what's going now with Iraq is like comparing apples with oranges.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "I", "think", "to", "compare", "what", "'s", "going", "now", "with", "Iraq", "is", "like", "comparing", "apples", "with", "oranges", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "What would Iran do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "Iran", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "I think the real question is what are we trying to achieve with whatever strikes the President may authorize.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "real", "question", "is", "what", "are", "we", "trying", "to", "achieve", "with", "whatever", "strikes", "the", "President", "may", "authorize", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "RBR", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Well, after the President of the United States draws that red line, after we heard very strong comments from the Secretary of state Today and later from the President today, if the U.S. were to do nothing militarily, what kind of message would that send?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "after", "the", "President", "of", "the", "United", "States", "draws", "that", "red", "line", ",", "after", "we", "heard", "very", "strong", "comments", "from", "the", "Secretary", "of", "state", "Today", "and", "later", "from", "the", "President", "today", ",", "if", "the", "U.S.", "were", "to", "do", "nothing", "militarily", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "message", "would", "that", "send", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "No, I think he has to do something because he basically said publicly some time ago, before the first attacks, chemical attacks earlier this year.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "he", "has", "to", "do", "something", "because", "he", "basically", "said", "publicly", "some", "time", "ago", ",", "before", "the", "first", "attacks", ",", "chemical", "attacks", "earlier", "this", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Today"], "LOCATION": ["United States", "U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Much more -- instead of just a few tomahawk cruise missiles, what else would you want him to do?", "question_tokens": ["Much", "more", "--", "instead", "of", "just", "a", "few", "tomahawk", "cruise", "missiles", ",", "what", "else", "would", "you", "want", "him", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", ":", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Well, I think there should be a -- I'm not an expert on what the target set might be.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "should", "be", "a", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "an", "expert", "on", "what", "the", "target", "set", "might", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Do you think it's possible U.S. intelligence is now flawed again?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "possible", "U.S.", "intelligence", "is", "now", "flawed", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "It doesn't sound like it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "sound", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "If the President signs the order, General Marks, how quickly for that order be implemented to target the various locations in Syria?", "question_tokens": ["If", "the", "President", "signs", "the", "order", ",", "General", "Marks", ",", "how", "quickly", "for", "that", "order", "be", "implemented", "to", "target", "the", "various", "locations", "in", "Syria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Wolf, all the targets have already been identified, the software has been uploaded so that the very latest targeting information has -- is available.", "answer_tokens": ["Wolf", ",", "all", "the", "targets", "have", "already", "been", "identified", ",", "the", "software", "has", "been", "uploaded", "so", "that", "the", "very", "latest", "targeting", "information", "has", "--", "is", "available", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["General Marks"], "LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "In other words all this publicity?", "question_tokens": ["In", "other", "words", "all", "this", "publicity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Well, I mean they have to have the publicity to go forward with this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", "they", "have", "to", "have", "the", "publicity", "to", "go", "forward", "with", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Is the President of United States who himself once taught law at the University of Chicago, a graduate of the Harvard Law School, is he potentially going to violate international law if you believe Jimmy Carter?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "President", "of", "United", "States", "who", "himself", "once", "taught", "law", "at", "the", "University", "of", "Chicago", ",", "a", "graduate", "of", "the", "Harvard", "Law", "School", ",", "is", "he", "potentially", "going", "to", "violate", "international", "law", "if", "you", "believe", "Jimmy", "Carter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["University of Chicago", "Harvard Law School"], "LOCATION": ["United States"], "PERSON": ["Jimmy Carter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Spider, the -- I know the President's intention is not to go in for anything more than a limited, very precise operation, but can he be 100 percent sure the U.S. won't be dragged into something much more substantial depending on the Syrian response?", "question_tokens": ["Spider", ",", "the", "--", "I", "know", "the", "President", "'s", "intention", "is", "not", "to", "go", "in", "for", "anything", "more", "than", "a", "limited", ",", "very", "precise", "operation", ",", "but", "can", "he", "be", "100", "percent", "sure", "the", "U.S.", "wo", "n't", "be", "dragged", "into", "something", "much", "more", "substantial", "depending", "on", "the", "Syrian", "response", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Wolf, if I would suggest, he should be a 100 percent convinced that the United States will be dragged into something that they choose not to be.", "answer_tokens": ["Wolf", ",", "if", "I", "would", "suggest", ",", "he", "should", "be", "a", "100", "percent", "convinced", "that", "the", "United", "States", "will", "be", "dragged", "into", "something", "that", "they", "choose", "not", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "What kind of marks, Fran, will you give the current national security team surrounding the President on this sensitive subject?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "marks", ",", "Fran", ",", "will", "you", "give", "the", "current", "national", "security", "team", "surrounding", "the", "President", "on", "this", "sensitive", "subject", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "You know, Wolf, because it seems clear to me that we are on the eve of decision to engage in military operations.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Wolf", ",", "because", "it", "seems", "clear", "to", "me", "that", "we", "are", "on", "the", "eve", "of", "decision", "to", "engage", "in", "military", "operations", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1941"]}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Alan", "Dershowitz", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Well, if that were the case, then every lawful act that has been taken by every president since 1941 will be unlawful.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "that", "were", "the", "case", ",", "then", "every", "lawful", "act", "that", "has", "been", "taken", "by", "every", "president", "since", "1941", "will", "be", "unlawful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "If you knew then what you know now, would you have played football, Jim?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "knew", "then", "what", "you", "know", "now", ",", "would", "you", "have", "played", "football", ",", "Jim", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Probably.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Do you believe, knowing what you know now that the NFL team doctors were looking out for the best interest of the players?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", ",", "knowing", "what", "you", "know", "now", "that", "the", "NFL", "team", "doctors", "were", "looking", "out", "for", "the", "best", "interest", "of", "the", "players", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "I don't think in all cases they were, no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "in", "all", "cases", "they", "were", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Is that why you're wearing the glasses right now, the sun glasses?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "why", "you", "'re", "wearing", "the", "glasses", "right", "now", ",", "the", "sun", "glasses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "No, I've been wearing sun glasses since I was 6 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "wearing", "sun", "glasses", "since", "I", "was", "6", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "The amount of money the players are going to receive?", "question_tokens": ["The", "amount", "of", "money", "the", "players", "are", "going", "to", "receive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I think it's a great result for a great group of people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "great", "result", "for", "a", "great", "group", "of", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "EX", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Larry how money you think Jim is going to receive as part of the settlement?", "question_tokens": ["Larry", "how", "money", "you", "think", "Jim", "is", "going", "to", "receive", "as", "part", "of", "the", "settlement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "No, there really isn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "there", "really", "is", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Is this sport safe?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "sport", "safe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I think they're finally realizing what, you know, what this -- the damage that can be done to the brain.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'re", "finally", "realizing", "what", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "this", "--", "the", "damage", "that", "can", "be", "done", "to", "the", "brain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]